Bloch, Edward J.; Papers apap115
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Congressional Campaigns, 1982-1996; Undated; 7; 0.50 cubic ft.
  - Pamphlets, Stickers, Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (7-Congressional Campaigns), Folder 8)
  - Rough Drafts and Notes, 1984-1987; Undated (Box 2 (7-Congressional Campaigns), Folder 9)
  - Campaign T-Shirt, Undated (Oversized 2)
  - Campaign Poster, Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Buttons, Undated (Oversized 4)
  - Large Campaign Poster, ca. 1980s (Oversized 5)
- Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance, 1990-2000; Undated; 8; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series consists of records dating from 1990 to 2000. It includes files on Ed Bloch's Interfaith Impact/ New York State Council of Churches activities. The majority of the series contains records from conferences, articles, and meeting minutes from the Interfaith Alliance.
  - Correspondence, 1996-2000; Undated (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 1-2)
  - Events and Events Announcements, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 3)
  - Income Statements, 1996-2000 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 4)
  - Interfaith Impact/ New York State Council of Churches, 1990-1996; Undated (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 5)
  - Mailing Lists, 1996; 1998 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 6)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1996-2001 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 7-8)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts, Board Member Lists, and Fact Sheets, Undated (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 9)
  - Mission Statement and By-laws, Undated (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 10)
  - National Association of Ecumenical Staff Conference, 1989 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 11)
  - News Clippings, 1998-2000 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 12)
  - Press Releases and Fliers, 1996-2000 (Box 1 (8-Interfaith Impact and Interfaith Alliance), Folder 13)
- Personal Correspondence and Papers, 1939-2001; Undated; 9; 0.53 cubic ft.
  This series concerns all of Bloch's personal papers and correspondence from 1939-2001, including non-campaign political materials, news clippings, church related materials, poetry, buttons, a calendar, essays, short stories, papers, Vietnam and veterans' related documents, and miscellaneous files.
  - Biographical Data, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1959-2001; Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 2)
  - Church Sermons and Papers, 1990-1999; Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 3)
  - Essays, Stories, Papers, 1959-2000 (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 4-5)
  - Essays, Stories, Papers, Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 6-7)
  - Memories of Fletcher, Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1985-2001; Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 10)
  - Photograph, 1981 (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 11)
  - Poetry, 1950-2001 (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 12)
  - Poetry, Undated (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 13)
  - Veterans' for Peace, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 14)
  - Vietnam Protest Marches, 1965-1967 (Box 1 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 15)
  - Bloch's Autobiography Courage Coward Courage!!, Two Copies, One Signed, Undated (Box 2 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 1)
  - Essays, Stories, Papers, Undated (Box 2 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 2)
  - Poetry, Undated (Box 2 (9-Personal Correspondence and Papers), Folder 3)
  - Gift from Presbyterian Church, "Elder Edward Bloch, Moderator 1993-1994, Albany Presbytery," (Oversized 2)
  - International Railway Workers Action Day Calendar, 2001 (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - Buttons and Pins, 1960-1980; Undated (Oversized 4)